dynomapper.com 2019-06-19

# Privacy Policy

This page represents our Privacy Policy, which informs users of the Personally Identifiable Information (PII) we collect, use, and share. In collecting and using this PII, the Data Protection Regulation is subject to a variety of rules governing how such activities may be carried out and the precautions that must be put in place to protect it.

The General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) governs the way Dyno Mapper carries out data processing activities. The GDPR is designed to protect the personal data of citizens of the European Union. Breaches in any way will attract weighty fines. With that in mind, this policy is set out to outline the steps Dyno Mapper is taking to ensure full compliance with this legislation.

**Table of Contents**  
[Information that We Collect From Users of Our Website and App](https://dynomapper.com/privacy-policy#Information "Information")  

##   
Introduction

Our Privacy Policy applies to our website, application, and all other Dyno Mapper features that collect information about you when you interact or use our services. This covers personal information that can be linked to you personally—like your telephone number, name, email address, password, and so forth.

This policy applies to all users, whether a trial user, subscriber, sub-user, customer, website visitor, participant, or use just a portion of our services. You decide on how we use your PII. These choices include how we can gain access to certain information and the limits in using it.

By creating an account with Dyno Mapper, visiting our website, or by using our services, you consent to the collection, use, and retention of your personal information as set forth in the terms of service of this Privacy Policy.

Dyno Mapper does not have control over information shared with third parties that have been copied or exported out of our terms of service or that you have personally shared with such ones outside of our terms of services. In such cases, the sole responsibly is left upon you to contact these third parties directly to have your information deleted, restricted, or retracted by other means.

###   
Changes to This Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy to reflect variations in features of our services, the law, advances in technology, and data collection practices. It is within your right to check this page periodically for such changes (if any). By the continued use of our services, you accept and agree to adhere to the updated policy.

NOTE: If you are not comfortable with the terms outlined in this privacy policy, please do not provide us any information about yourself, or try to access or use our services.

##   
Information that We Collect From Users of Our Blog, Website, and App

We only collect information that is necessary to provide and improve Dyno Mapper's services. We take the privacy of everyone seriously. When users sign up or register on this site, they may be asked to provide certain personal information such as their name, credit card information, email address, or other details to facilitate a smooth transaction or experience.

When this information is collected, it is stored and associated with your account unless otherwise noted. We will only use and disclose your information as outlined in this Privacy Policy.

###   
Registration and Profile Information

We collect information about you that is necessary for the smooth operation of a service or to fulfill a transaction, which includes your name, email address, password, IP, and other information that is necessary for a complete profile. You reserve the right to modify your profile—alter or remove part or all your basic personal information.

You decide on the information that you give to us, but as a participant, providing accurate profile information helps you get more out of our services.

###   
Uploading, Posting and Providing Content

We collect your personal information to provide you with Dyno Mapper's services when you fill out a form, upload, post, send, receive, share information, or use our app. This information is what you choose to include and you never have to share personal data, though it may limit your user experience or how successfully we deliver our services.

###   
Customer Support

Our website includes the convenient feature of customer support. Contacting Dyno Mapper through email, live chat, or any other means, will prompt you to provide your contact information, details about your inquiry, or other information deemed necessary to allow us to resolve your problem.

###   
Payment Information

For users of our services, we process all payment information (credit card and/or PayPal email address) through a secure payment system—Braintree/Paypal API. Payment details (credit card, billing, or contact information) are not stored on our servers. You may choose not to provide this information, but it will hinder you from fulfilling your desired goal of making a purchase.

###   
Information Received From Other Sources

We may receive your personal information by other means, including users from third-party services, users of our services, affiliates, and partners. Your information may also be passed on by other users when they provide information about you through our services. For example—as a subscriber of our application— you may interact with other associates or employees by inviting them as sub-account holders where a username and email is required.

If you share your personal information with these users, it's a possibility that they will share it with us within the content that they post on our website. If you do not wish to divulge personal information to other users, do not share your information publicly.

###   
Third Party Products and Services

By integrating or linking with a third party service like Facebook, LinkedIn or Google, when creating an account with Dyno Mapper, we will receive your name, email, and other personal information about you—permitted and embedded in the settings of these services. We do not have control over the privacy policies controlled by these third-party services, so be sure to review all privacy terms and conditions by them to be certain of what information may be shared with us before moving forward.

#### Google

We currently participate in Google AdSense revenue sharing for display of ads on our Blog. We also use Google Adwords to target website users that have opted-in to online advertising. By logging into their MyAccount, users can opt-in for this type of advertising at any time. Google's Advertising Principles can be found [here](https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/6008942?hl=en&visit_id=1-636628064842044955-118304472&rd=1 "here") for your review.

#### California Online Privacy Protection Act (CalOPPA)

The [CalOPPA](http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf) requires that online services and commercial websites that collect personally identifiable information post a privacy policy. Those in breach of their requirements are at risk of civil litigation under California's Unfair Competition Law.

In compliance with the CalOPPA, we agree to the following:

  * Anonymous user visits if wanted.

  * A link to the site privacy policy will be on the site’s home page, or on the first significant page after entering the site.

  * The Privacy Policy link includes the word 'Privacy', and is easily located on the specified page.

Notification of privacy policy changes will be placed on our Privacy Policy Page.

Users will be able to change personal information by logging in to their account.

### How are do-not-track signals handled by this site?

Do not track signals are honored and this site will not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is being employed by a user.

### Does this site allow third party behavioral tracking?.

Our application uses Google Adwords to retarget advertising to visitors on our website on the Google Search network. Users will have the option to opt out of this type of advertising in their MyAccount.

### COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)

Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) allows parents to control the collection of PII of children under 13. The COPPA regulation is enforced by the Federal Trade Commission, the nation's consumer protection agency. This regulation specifies what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children's privacy and safety online.

We do not specifically market to children under 13.

#### Fair Information Practices

In compliance with Fair Information Practices the following responsive action shall be implemented, should a breach of data occur:

Users will be notified via email within 7 business days.

This site agrees to the individual redress principle. This principle requires that individuals have actual enforceable rights against data users. It also requires that individuals have recourse in the courts or via a government agency which will investigate and if necessary, prosecute any non-compliance by data processors.

#### CAN SPAM Act

The CAN-SPAM Act regulates commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, affords recipients the right to stop emails being sent to them, and specifies the penalty for violations.

This site collects your email address to:

  * Deliver information, and inquiry responses
  * Order processing, other logistics, and updates pertaining to orders
  * Marketing our services to clients after original transactions

In compliance with CANSPAM, we agree to the following:

  * False, or misleading subjects or email addresses will not be used
  * Messages will be identified as advertising.
  * The physical address of our business or site headquarters will be included
  * Third party email marketing services will be checked for compliance if used.
  * Quickly implement and Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests
  * Provide a link at the bottom of each email to unsubscribe from emails

### Partners and Affiliates

We may receive your personal information from partners and affiliates if you have given them permission to share your information with others, or if it was obtained from public resources. Dyno Mapper may participate in data enrichment—sharing some information about you with third party vendors (e.g. QuickBooks accounting software), as a means of managing our business more effectively. For example, your email address may be shared in order to obtain your company name; however, a Data Protection Agreement is signed with third party vendors to ensure your data is protected and lawfully obtained.

### Information Collected Indirectly

Certain information is collected automatically when using our services.

#### Use of our services.

Usage data is logged when you visit our site, use our app or other features owned by Dyno Mapper. These include a login, a clicked link, file upload, viewed content, or interaction with other users.

#### Connection information, device, and location.

Data is collected from devices and networks—such as your smartphone, tablet, or other devices—used to access our services. Information about the browser used, hardware, OS, and device features is some of the information that may be collected when an app is downloaded or a link is clicked when accessing our services. Other statistics such as your IP address, network provider or carrier, and proxy server may also be obtained to provide you with a better user experience.

#### Cookies and other tracking technologies.

Cookies and other web-tracking technologies are used to identify your devices when using our services. Cookies are small files that a service provider or website transfers to a user's hard drive (with their permission) to facilitate the service provider or site's ability to collect or retain certain information. As an example, when making a purchase, a site may employ the use of cookies to process and remember certain items placed in the shopping cart.

The website may also use cookies to recognize user preferences based on their activities. All of this is done in an effort to deliver improved services. Cookies may also be employed to compile site traffic data and interaction for the continuous use of tools and for a better user experience.

Dyno Mapper may use trusted third parties to track and collect this information. Depending on your browser settings, you can set your computer or device to alert you when a cookie is being sent, or block it entirely. 

If cookies are disabled, please note that some features—like your login and user sessions—may be disabled as well.

## How Collected Information is Used

Dyno Mapper uses information to support, provide, personalize, and develop its services. The way in which this information is used depends on the type of service you choose, how you use it, and your preferences. Below is a detailed outline as to how your information is collected and legitimately utilized on our platform.

### To Provide our Services

The information collected from you is used to facilitate our services—processing your transactions, authorizing access to our services, as well as operating and maintaining our services. For example, your credit card and billing information are used to carry out a paid transaction.

### For Communication

Contact information is used to send transactional messages via email, push notifications or other means employed by our services. An email may be sent to communicate information regarding a transaction, due date reminders, or other notifications. For direct customers, communication messages are sent to confirm purchases, help with a reported issue, or provide general support.

Unique messages are sent to each user based on how our services are utilized. For example, we may communicate to a user to inform on how a certain service is used or even make a suggestion on how to improve on user-experience. Most transactional messages are mandatory and you cannot opt out of them.

### For Marketing or Promotional Services

Your information may be used to send promotional email messages that may interest you. These messages serve the purpose of improving our services or allowing you the opportunity to learn more about what we offer. Examples include information about new products and features, newsletters, notifications, and surfing this site. An unsubscribe link is placed at the bottom of each promotional email.

### For Research Purposes

As we work to improve our services, we often conduct research to make them more useful to customers and users of our website. Direct customer feedback and data is used to improve our services through testing, data analytics, and research.

### For Customer Support

We collect and use your information to help fix problems such as bugs, data crashes, and logs—and to communicate with you.

### For Security Purposes

We intend to secure your personal information in the best way possible. We use your information to verify account activities, monitor, investigate or prevent fraud, and to keep abreast of possible violations of our policies.

### To Protect Our Legal Rights and Interests or When Required By Law

To work along with legal claims, regulations, investigations, or to protect your (and our) legal rights or make audits, we will require the use of your information. Your information may also be disclosed in the process of acquisition of our assets or business, or in the event of a merger.

### With Your Permission

The most likely use of your information is in the case where it is given to us by your consent. For example, we may ask for your information to participate in a survey to see how we can better improve our services to customers.

### For the Processing of Legitimate Legality Regarding EEA Users

The legal basics surrounding how we use and collect your information is dependent on how you employ our services. For users located within the European Economic Area (EEA), their information is collected and used in compliance with EU laws. Your information will only be collected and used under the following circumstances:

  * Your data is needed to operate one of our requested services or to fulfill a contract.
  * To protect your rights and freedom—monitor, protect, or investigate security threats or fraud.
  * For the protection of our legal rights.
  * In compliance with certain laws.
  * For customer support inquiries.
  * For the management of corporate transactions, like acquisitions and mergers.
  * To research, understand, or improve upon our customer relationships or business.
  * With your consent to carry out specific dealings.

In cases where we rely on your consent for the processing of your personal information, it is within your rights to decline or withdraw your consent at any time—except for processes that have already occurred. However, you may object to us using your information in cases where we rely on legitimate interest, if so you will not have access to the use of our services.

For more information or if you have questions about how your information is collected and used, please email us at [support@dynomapper.com](mailto:support@dynomapper.com) or write to our physical location:

DYNO Mapper

c/o Indigo Design Co.  
222 W. Merchandise Mart Plaza Suite 1212  
Chicago, IL 60654

## How Collected Information is Shared

Personally identifiable information is not sold, traded, or otherwise transferred to outside parties except for the purposes outlined below.

### Customers and Public Forums

You are free to share your information with other users when you participate in blog commenting, forum posting, and other applicable features of our site. All information—your image, messages, etc., may be read and used by other members that have access to these sections. Be mindful though that publicly shared personal information is done at your own risk—we will not take responsibility for any mishaps incurred during the process.

### Third Parties

In an effort to provide better services, we may share certain information about you with third party associates.

### Service Providers

To help provide and maintain our services—payment processing, business analytics, web app development, marketing, customer support, hosting, and data storage—we collaborate with third party service providers. To perform their duties on our behalf, these providers will need access to your information, under the obligation that it will not be disclosed or used for any other purposes.

### Third Party Apps, Sites, and Widgets

From time-to-time, you may encounter direct links (with different privacy policies) on our website that lead to other sites, services, or apps. By clicking on these external links/third party vendors or participating and making contact with them, you have the opportunity to review and agree to the terms of services employed by their company. Any information you submit through their website or app is controlled and governed by their privacy policies.

To protect your Personally Identifiable Information (PII), it is advised that you add extra security to your Personal Identifiable Info. Where the host requires your legitimate information, this should be communicated and understood before making further advancements.

We also use third party widgets and plugins to provide additional features and functionalities—like social media share buttons. These tools collect information about your website activities by means of cookies and the collection of your IP address, to decipher the most-visited pages on our site. Their company's privacy policies govern your interaction with these tools, so be mindful of that.

### A Financing Event, Merger, or Sale

Your information may also be disclosed during a sale, merger, or acquisition process of our assets or business. However, you will be notified by email or other public areas on our website, along with the choices open to you regarding how your information may be treated.

## Information Security and Retention

### Security of Your Information

Our site is scanned and tested regularly in order to keep up with the most current protective internet practices to safeguard your information. We use various trusted hosting providers to protect your information and prevent loss and misuse of your data. Infrastructures such as hardware and software firewalls, Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology, data encryption, backups, identity and access control, and other security measures are employed to safeguard your trust.

However, no security system is impenetrable. Although we try our best to keep your data secure and private, we cannot guarantee full protection of your provided information because of the nature of the internet and its inherent risks.

### Retention of Your Information

As long as your account is active or open with us, we will need your information to continue our operations. Some of your information will be retained to enforce our rights and agreements, comply with business or legal obligations, maintain security, and any other actions deemed necessary or permitted by law.

If your account has expired or has been canceled, or when those terms are no longer in force, you will have the option of anonymizing your personal information using controls located within your MyAccount page.

## The Right to Access and Control Your Information

It is within your rights to access and control your own personal data. You are free to make changes to, access, or delete your personal information and stipulate whether such data is collected, used, and shared. This section will highlight details on how you can make requests and exercise your rights in regards to the control and access to your information. All of these choices can be done in your account settings within your MyAccount page.

The deletion of some information may not be fulfilled. For instance the removal of information that is a necessary part of our privacy policy—information that is permitted by law to maintain legitimate interests. For data that is controlled by third parties, you'll have to contact them to have your information deleted or restricted.

### Editing Your Personal Information

You can change or correct your personal information at any time through your account settings within your MyAccount page. Such changes may be necessary if your profile information is inaccurate or outdated.

#### Deleting Your Information

You can delete certain information about yourself through your account—content that you may have submitted through surveys. If you are having trouble deleting this information, feel free to contact our support team for help.

### Data Portability

You can always obtain a copy of your personal information from us in a machine-readable format. Depending on the contract, it is within your rights to transfer that information to another service provider. Upon request, we will provide you with a machine-readable format of your basic account information that is permitted for transfer based on our legal basis for processing.

### Terminating Your Account

You can terminate your account and discontinue our services at any time by logging in and visiting the cancellation page. If you encounter issues logging in, contact our support team directly at [support@dynomapper.com](mailto:support@dynomapper.com). Please note that some of your information may be withheld for legal purposes, to maintain security, to endorse our rights, to fulfill regulatory requirements, to allow you to unsubscribe if necessary, or to prevent abuse or fraud. Information that was shared to third-party platforms (bug reports, surveys, feedbacks, messages or reports) will remain visible to them through an anonymous account.

### Request That We No Longer Access, Store, or Use Your Information

You may log into your MyAccount page and request that we limit the use of your information, no longer use, access, store, or otherwise process your information. Your consent to use your information can be withdrawn. In cases where there is a dispute over the use of information we will limit further use until the dispute is settled.

### Opt Out of Communications

Changing the settings within your MyAccount or by using the unsubscribe link in each email, will enable you to opt out of promotional emails. However, you may still receive general emails regarding transactions, terms of use, and our services.

### Remove or Turn Off Cookies

You can easily discontinue the use of or remove cookie settings from within your browser. Please see the relevant section in this privacy policy regarding the use of cookies.

## Transferring Information Internationally

Global information is collected and used but stored in the United States. So by using our services—you consent to the processing and transfer of your information to the United States. Where applicable, your information may also be transferred, processed, or stored wherever our third-party providers operate, which may not be in the United States or the country in which you reside. In addition, you may not have data protection laws that provide the same level of protection like that of the General Data Protection Regulation which protects nations in the European Economic Area. However, as your consent is voluntary, you have the right to revoke or discontinue the use of our services at any time. To opt out, please log into your MyAccount page or contact us at [support@dynomapper.com](mailto:support@DYNOmapper.com) if you are having trouble doing so.

## Contacting Us

If you have questions about this privacy policy, wish to file a complaint or to resolve an issue, you may contact us using the information below.

Email address: [support@dynomapper.com](mailto:support@DYNOmapper.com)

Telephone number: 1-866-389-4643

Physical mail:   
DYNO Mapper  
c/o Indigo Design Co.  
222 W. Merchandise Mart Plaza Suite 1212  
Chicago, IL 60654
